Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2011; 2399 Volumes
  - Dungeons and Dragons, 44
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons Player's Handbook, 2nd edition (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 48)
    - Adventures in Blackmoor (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 601)
    - Arena of Thyatis (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 860)
    - Arms and Equipment Guide (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 73)
    - Bastion of Broken Souls (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 103)
    - Blizzard Pass (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1133)
    - Book of Challenges: Dungeon Rooms, Puzzles, and Traps (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 106)
    - Book of Exalted Deeds (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 72)
    - Book of Vile Darkness (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 56)
    - Campaign Hexagon System, City State (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1775)
    - Castle Caldwell and Beyond (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 596)
    - Character and Monster Assortment (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 609)
    - Character Sheets (no place: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 55)
    - Citadel of Fire (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1537)
    - City State of the Invincible Overlord, Revised ed. (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1458)
    - City State of the World Emperor (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1455)
    - Complete Warrior: A Player's Guide to Combat for All Classes (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 69)
    - Conversion Manual (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 57)
    - Creature Catalog (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 857)
    - Crown of Ancient Glory (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 870)
    - Curse of Xanathon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 875)
    - Death's Ride (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 600)
    - Deep Horizon (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 100)
    - Defenders of the Faith: A Guidebook to Clerics and Paladins (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 87)
    - Deities and Demigods (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 59)
    - Deluxe Character Sheets (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 89)
    - Deluxe Dungeon Master's Screen (no place: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 66)
    - Desert of Desolation (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 78)
    - Drums on Fire Mountain (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 868)
    - Dungeon Master Screen (no place: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 54)
    - Dungeon Master's Guide II (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2005 (Volume 64)
    - Dungeon Master's Guide: Core Rulebook II, 3.5 edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 63)
    - Dungeon Master's Guide: Core Rulebook II, 3rd edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 51)
    - Dungeon Module B2: The Keep on the Borderlands (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 605)
    - Dungeon Module B3: Palace of the Silver Princess (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 599)
    - Dungeon Module B4: The Lost City (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 598)
    - Dungeon Module BI: In Search of the Unknown (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 604)
    - Earthshaker! (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 602)
    - Enemies and Allies (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 99)
    - Fiend Folio (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 71)
    - Frontier Forts of Kelnore (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1767)
    - Frostburn: Mastering the Perils of Ice and Snow (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2004 (Volume 68)
    - Furioso (Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1687)
    - Gazetteer (no place: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 84)
    - Gen Con IX Dungeons (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1497)
    - Heart of Nightfang Spire (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 98)
    - Hero Builders Guidebook (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 95)
    - Horror on the Hill (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 597)
    - In Search of New Gods (Kimberly, Notts: GameMaster Publications), 1986 (Volume 1652)
    - Into the Maelstrom (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 861)
    - King's Festival (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 874)
    - Lathan's Gold (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1142)
    - Legions of Thyatis (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 859)
    - Living Greyhawk Gazetteer (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 97)
    - Lord of the Iron Fortress (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 102)
    - Manual of the Planes (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 61)
    - Master of the Desert Nomads (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 864)
    - Masters of the Wild: A Guidebook to Barbarians, Druids, and Rangers (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 104)
    - Maze of the Riddling Minotaur (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1171)
    - Modron (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1554)
    - Monster Manual II (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 58)
    - Monster Manual III (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2004 (Volume 65)
    - Monster Manual: Core Rulebook III, 3.5 edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 67)
    - Monster Manual: Core Rulebook III, 3rd edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 52)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Kara-Tur Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), undated (Volume 90)
    - Mystery of the Snow Pearls (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 603)
    - Night's Dark Terror (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 873)
    - Of Skulls and Scrapfaggot Green (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1512)
    - Operation Ogre (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1486)
    - Oriental Adventures: Blood of the Yakuza (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 82)
    - Oriental Adventures: Night of the Seven Swords (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 80)
    - Oriental Adventures: Ochimo The Sprit Warrior (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 81)
    - Oriental Adventures: Swords of the Daimyo (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 79)
    - Oriental Advenures (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 60)
    - Outdoor Geomorphs (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1977 (Volume 1756)
      maps
    - Player's Handbook: Core Rulebook I, 3.5 edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 70)
    - Player's Handbook: Core Rulebook I, 3rd edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 53)
    - Poor Wizard's Almanac II: Book of Facts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 471)
    - Poor Wizard's Almanac III: Book of Facts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 472)
    - Poor Wizard's Almanac: Book of Facts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 400)
    - Psionics Handbook (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 62)
    - Quagmire! (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 866)
    - Quest for the Heartstone (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1141)
    - Ready Ref Sheets (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1765)
    - Return to the Temple of Elemental Evil (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 85)
    - Rod of Serraillian (Kimberly, Notts: GameMaster Publications), 1987 (Volume 1647)
    - Sabre River (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 606)
    - Savage Species: Playing Monstrous Characters (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 74)
    - Song and Silence: A Guidebook to Bards and Rogues (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 101)
    - Spies of Lightelf (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1550)
    - Stronghold Builders Guidebook (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 105)
    - Survival of the Fittest (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1487)
    - Sword and Fist: A guidebook to Fighters and Monks (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 94)
    - Sword of Hope (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1490)
    - Talons of Night (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 863)
    - Temple of Death (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 865)
    - Test of the Warlords (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 871)
    - The Awakening (Kimberly, Notts: GameMaster Publications), 1986 (Volume 1651)
    - The Bloodstone Wars (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 75)
    - The Book of Marvelous Magic (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 608)
    - The Book of Treasure Maps (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1547)
    - The Book of Treasure Maps II (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1565)
    - The Caverns of Thracia (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1553)
    - The Dragon Crown (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1510)
    - The Fantastic Wilderlands Beyonde (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1754)
    - The Forge of Fury (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 92)
    - The Fright at Tristor (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 96)
    - The Gem and the Staff (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1143)
    - The Mines of Bloodstone (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 76)
    - The Mines of Custalcon (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1551)
    - The Nine Doctrines of Darkness: The Second Adventure (Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1683)
    - The Savage Coast (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 869)
    - The Shady Dragon Inn (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1450)
    - The Shattered Statue (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 77)
    - The Speaker in Dreams: An Adventure for 5th-Level Characters (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 91)
    - The Standing Stone: An Adventure for 7th-Level Characters (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 88)
    - The Sunless Citadel (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 93)
    - The Thieves of Fortress Badabaskor (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1974 (Volume 1511)
    - The Tree of Life (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 607)
    - The Unknown Gods (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1536)
    - The Veiled Soceity (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 872)
    - The War of Rafts of Kron (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 867)
    - Tome and Blood: A Guidebook to Wizards and Sorcerers (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 86)
    - Tower of Ulission (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1489)
    - Treasure Hunt (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 83)
    - Under the Storm Giant's Castle (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1485)
    - Vengeance of Alphaks (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 862)
    - Verbosh (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1491)
    - What is Dungeons and Dragons? (New York, NY: Warner Books), 1982 (Volume 1796)
      By John Butterfield, Philip Parker, and Daid Honigmann
    - Wilderlands of High Fantasy (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1463)
    - Wilderlands of the Fantastic Reaches (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1456)
    - Wilderlands of the Magic Realm (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1753)
    - Wrath of the Minotaur (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 916)
  - Earthdawn, 45
    - Arcane Mysteris of Barsaive (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1997 (Volume 1405)
    - Blades (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1995 (Volume 1395)
    - Creatures of Barsaive (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1372)
    - Crystal Raiders of Barsaive (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1998 (Volume 1408)
    - Denizens of Earthdawn: Volume 1 (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1376)
    - Denizens of Earthdawn: Volume 2 (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1375)
    - Earthdawn (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1409)
    - Earthdawn Companion (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1382)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 5 (Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications), 1995 (Volume 1609)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 6 (Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications), 1996 (Volume 1608)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 8 (Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications), 1997 (Volume 1607)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 9 (Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications), 1997 (Volume 1606)
    - Earthdawn: The Age of Legend, Hardcover (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1993 (Volume 1595)
    - Earthdawn: The Age of Legend, Paperback (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1617)
    - GameMaster Pack (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1993 (Volume M4)
    - Horrors (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1995 (Volume 1374)
    - Infected (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1379)
    - Legends of Earthdawn (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1995 (Volume 1373)
    - Magic: A Manual of Mystic Secrets (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1394)
    - Mists of Betrayal (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1993 (Volume 1381)
    - Parlainth Adventures (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1378)
    - Prelude to War (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1401)
    - Shattered Pattern (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1377)
    - Sky Point Adventures (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1995 (Volume 1396)
    - Terror in the Skies (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1994 (Volume 1380)
    - The Adept's Way (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1995 (Volume 1371)
    - The Blood Wood (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1997 (Volume 1402)
    - The Book of Exploration (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1397)
    - The Earthdawn Survival Guide (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1399)
    - The Ork Nation of Cara Fahd (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1998 (Volume 1404)
    - The Secret Societies of Barsaive (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1997 (Volume 1407)
    - The Serpent River (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1398)
    - The Theran Empire (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1997 (Volume 1406)
    - Throal Adventures (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1400)
    - Throal: The Dwarf Kingdom (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1996 (Volume 1403)
  - Element Masters, 46
    - Player's Manual, 1st ed. (Virginia Beach, VA: Escape Ventures), 1982 (Volume 1670)
      Autographed copy
    - The First Border Patrol (Virginia Beach, VA: Escape Ventures), 1982 (Volume 1671)
  - Elfquest, 47
    - Elfquest: The Official Roleplaying Game, 2nd edition (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1989 (Volume 382)
  - Elric!, 48
    - Atlas of the Young Kingdoms Vol. I: The Northern Continent (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 250)
    - Elric (Albany, CA: The Chaosium), 1977 (Volume M4)
    - Elric! Dark Fantasy Roleplaying Game (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 256)
    - Elric! Gamemaster Screen (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 253)
    - Fate of Fools: Pawns of Destiny (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1994 (Volume 252)
    - Melnibone: Dragon Isle and Dreaming City (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 255)
    - The Bronze Grimoire: Magic and the Supernatural (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1994 (Volume 251)
    - The Unknown East: Forgotten Foes of the Bright Empire (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 254)
  - Encyclopedia Harnica, 49
    - Cities of Harn (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1987 (Volume 1193)
    - Cities of Harn: Son of Cities (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1987 (Volume 1192)
    - Encyclopedia Harnica 4 (Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications), 1984 (Volume 1191)
    - Olokand, Atlas Harnica, and Manor (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1984 (Volume 1190)
  - Epxae Islands Mysteries, 50
    - Stones of the Selt, 2nd ed. (Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press), 1981 (Volume 1627)
  - Espionage, 51
    - Border Crossing (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1983 (Volume 2117)
    - Stormhaven (#3301) (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 2144)
  - Fading Suns, 52
    - Byzantium Secundus (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1996 (Volume 721)
    - Children of the Gods: Obun and Ukar (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1998 (Volume 713)
    - Fading Suns (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1995 (Volume 741)
    - Fading Suns: Player's Companion (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1997 (Volume 716)
    - Forbidden Lore (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1996 (Volume 720)
    - Lords of the Known Worlds (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1996 (Volume 719)
    - Merchants of the Jumpweb (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1997 (Volume 714)
    - Priests of the Celestial Sun (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1996 (Volume 717)
    - Sinners and Saints (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1998 (Volume 712)
    - The Dark Between the Stars (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1997 (Volume 715)
    - Weapon Compendium (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1996 (Volume 708)
    - Weird Places (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1996 (Volume 718)
  - Fantasy Hero, 53
    - Fantasy Hero Companion (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2264)
    - Fantasy Hero Companion II (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 2262)
    - Magic Items: A Magical Supplement (#29) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 2127)
    - The Roleplaying Game of Epic Adventure: Fantasy Hero (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1984 (Volume 2132)
    - The Spell Book (#41) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 2106)
  - Fantasy Master, 54
    - Aesheba: Greek Africa (Lake Geneva, WI: New Infinities Productions, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1298)
  - Fiend Folio, 55
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 811)
  - Flash Gordon, 56
    - Flash Gordon and the Warriors of Mongo (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1977 (Volume 1681)
  - Foreign Legion, 57
    - Macta (Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications), 1979 (Volume M5)
    - Moulay Ishmael (Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications), 1979 (Volume M5)
  - Forgotten Realms, 58
    - Castle Spulzeer (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 321)
    - Adventures (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 185)
    - Anauroch (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 190)
    - Aurora's Whole Realms Catalogue (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 390)
    - Black Courser (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 355)
    - Blood Charge (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 354)
    - Book of Lairs (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 343)
    - Calimport (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 226)
    - Champions of Ruin, 1st edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2005 (Volume 175)
    - Champions of Valor, 1st edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2005 (Volume 172)
    - City of Gold (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 357)
    - City of Splendors: Waterdeep, 1st edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2005 (Volume 174)
    - City of the Spider Queen (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 296)
    - Cloak and Dagger (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 303)
    - Cormanthyr: Empire of the Elves (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 324)
    - Cormyr (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 229)
    - Cormyr: The Tearing of the Weave, 1st edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2007 (Volume 168)
    - Cult of the Dragon (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 320)
    - Curse of the Azure Bonds (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 210)
    - Demihuman Deities (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 313)
    - Demihumans of the Realms (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 314)
    - Doom of Daggerdale (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 202)
    - Draconomicon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 351)
    - Dragons of Faerun (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2006 (Volume 294)
    - Dreams of the Red Wizard (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 196)
    - Drizzt Do'Urden's Guide to the Underdark (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 305)
    - Dungeon Crawl Undermountain Maddgoth's Castle (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 341)
    - Dungeon Crawl Undermountain Stardock (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 340)
    - Dungeon Crawl Undermountain The Lost Level (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 342)
    - Dungeon Master's Screen ( no place: Wizards of the Coast), undated (Volume 299)
    - Dungeons and Dragons Campaign Setting: Forgotten Realms (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 179)
    - Dwarves Deep (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 192)
    - Elminster's Ecologies Appendix I: The Battle of Bones, Hill of Lost Souls (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 329)
    - Elminster's Ecologies Appendix II: The High Moor, The Serpent Hills (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 328)
    - Elves of Evermeet (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 347)
    - Empires of the Sands (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 199)
    - Endless Armies (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 358)
    - Faith and Pantheons, 1st edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 184)
    - Faiths and Avatars (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1996 (Volume 317)
    - Fires of Zatal (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 359)
    - For Duty and Deity (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 318)
    - Four from Cormyr (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 323)
    - Gateway to Ravens Bluff, the Living City (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 220)
    - Giantcraft (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 345)
    - Gold and Glory (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 188)
    - Hall of Heroes (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 195)
    - Halls of the High King (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 206)
    - Haunted Halls of Eveningstar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 204)
    - Hellgate Keep (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 319)
    - Heroes' Lorebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 332)
    - Horde Campaign (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 191)
    - Hordes of Dragonspear (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 203)
    - How the Mighty are Fallen (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1996 (Volume 326)
    - Inside Ravens Bluff, the Living City (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 219)
    - Kara-Tur Trail Map (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 391)
    - Kidnapped (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 311)
    - Lord of Darkness (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 297)
    - Lords of Darkness (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 353)
    - Lost Empires of Faerun, 1st edition (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2005 (Volume 176)
    - Mad Monkey vs. The Dragon Claw (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 216)
    - Magic of Faerun (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 298)
    - Marco Volo Arrival (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 334)
    - Marco Volo Departure (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 336)
    - Marco Volo Journey (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 335)
    - Monster Compendium: Monsters of Faerun (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 300)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 812)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 815)
    - Moonshae (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 200)